<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Frontop Engineering Limited</title>
    <link>https://frontop.github.io/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Frontop Engineering Limited</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://frontop.github.io/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering design</title>
      <link>https://frontop.github.io/services/engineering-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frontop.github.io/services/engineering-design/</guid>
      <description>Buildings define contemporary urban lives and shape city images. Knowing that the place you live and work in is safe and comfortable is a basic necessity for every person. Frontop understands how building performance could interact with people&amp;rsquo;s daily work and life. We continue to endeavour in achieving our clients&amp;rsquo; needs and expectations through embedding state-of-the-art technology in our building designs. Our motivation for success is driven by our client’s satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Engineering</title>
      <link>https://frontop.github.io/services/environmental-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frontop.github.io/services/environmental-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Soil and Groundwater Chemical Testing Result Analysis and Reporting Environmental Site Assessments (Phase I, II &amp;amp; III) Contaminant Site Cleanup and Decommissioning Soil and Groundwater Remediation Contaminant Transport Groundwater Monitoring Peer Reviews Feasibility and Cost-Benefit Evaluation Record of Site Condition (RSC)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geotechnical Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://frontop.github.io/services/geotechnical-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frontop.github.io/services/geotechnical-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>As our primary form of service, Geotechnical Instrumentation and Monitoring is Frontop’s main area of expertise. Our years of experience and knowledge guarantees that our clients receive accurate and high-quality work. We have shown strong monitoring performance on our previous projects for TTC subway tunnels, subway stations, Metrolinx, CN Railways grade seperation and many other government infrastructures. Frontop’s extensive monitoring program that includes design, instrument installation, data collection, reporting and real time web-based data access, ensures that the client’s needs are fully satisfied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydrogeological Engineering</title>
      <link>https://frontop.github.io/services/hydrogeological-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frontop.github.io/services/hydrogeological-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Percolation Testing Design and Construction of Monitoring Networks and Monitoring Wells PTTW (Permit To Take Water) Application Hydrogeological Study and Assessment for Residential Subdivision and Environmental Projects Water Sample Chemical Testing Result Analysis and Reporting Underground Water Investigation and Mapping Development of Groundwater Supplies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Material Testing</title>
      <link>https://frontop.github.io/services/material-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frontop.github.io/services/material-testing/</guid>
      <description>Similar to all types of foundations in life, foundations in construction are the most important aspect of a structure. A solid and well built foundation is the first and most important step in the building process. Geotechnical engineering is concerned with the behaviour of earth materials occurring on the surface and below ground. A good understanding of soil and rock mechanics can help determine all relevant properties of the material and evaluate how they respond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noise and Vibration Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://frontop.github.io/services/noise-and-vibration-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frontop.github.io/services/noise-and-vibration-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>Our fully self-developed noise and vibration monitoring system is a robust, cost efficient solution for outdoor and indoor noise and vibration monitoring. Features include:
Viewing data online from anywhere Listening to recorded events Getting notified by email or SMS when thresholds are reached Variable data recordings and transmission intervals Use wireless technology (Wifi, GPRS or 3G/4G)
Noise and vibration are two of the main concerns affecting workers health and public safety during construction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>